Guide to the Duke University Archives Photographic Negative Collection, 1855-1995
University Archives Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- Subject Negatives
  - Subject: Departments - Anthropology
    - Departments - Anthropology, LaBarre case, 1963 April
    - Departments - Anthropology, statue, 1963 May
    - Departments - Anthropology, Harley collection, African, 1964 December
    - Departments - Anthropology, Princeton exhibit, 1965 May
    - Departments - Anthropology, Princeton exhibit, with girl, 1965 May
    - Departments - Anthropology, Dr. LaBarre exhibit cases, 1968 October
    - Departments - Anthropology, cases, 1968
    - Departments - Anthropology, LaBarre exhibit cases, 1973 February
    - Departments - Anthropology, exhibit, January
    - Departments - Anthropology, LaBarre cases, 1967 February
    - Departments - Anthropology, LaBarre exhibit cases, 1966 November
    - Departments - Anthropology, Israel dig, 1975
    - Departments - Anthropology, Israel dig, 1977 September
    - Departments - Anthropology, fossil, 1975 May
  - Subject: Departments - Art
    - Departments - Art, statue under floriscope, art museum, 1968 August
    - Departments - Art, first collection for university museum, 1964 May
    - Departments - Art, sidewalk art exhibit, 1964 May
    - Departments - Art, Fine Arts, Aesthetics
    - Departments - Art, student art sculpture, 1969 June
    - Departments - Art, sculpture, 1969 September
    - Departments - Art, presentation, Grecian urn, Mrs. Semans to Dr. Knight, 1964 October
    - Departments - Art, girls and pots, 1966 February
    - Departments - Art, alumni lounge, 1964 February
    - Departments - Art, sidewalk art, Sir Reid, 1960 May
    - Departments - Art, Edith London, exhibit, 1968 March
    - Departments - Art, Art 62, house models, 1950 May 19
    - Departments - Art, London exhibit, 1964 March
    - Departments - Art, Scholz Collection, 1965 April
    - Departments - Art, delivery, 5 million exhibit, 1966 June
    - Departments - Art, Broomer art collection restorer, Russian, 1966 January
    - Departments - Art, N. Pratt exhibit, East Campus, 1966 November
    - Departments - Art, Dalton exhibit, 1963 November
    - Departments - Art, Japanese print exhibit, 1962 July
    - Departments - Art, Patrick and art exhibit, 1962 July
    - Departments - Art, exhibit, 1965 March
    - Departments - Art, exhibit, alumni lounge, 1965 September-October
    - Departments - Art, Tamarind, exhibit, 1965 January
    - Departments - Art, South American exhibit, 1962 March
    - Departments - Art, copies for Meuller, 1961 November
    - Departments - Art, exhibit, East Campus library
    - Departments - Art, sidewalk exhibit, 1960 May
    - Departments - Art, Chinese art, 1960
    - Departments - Art, Japanese art exhibit, 1960
    - Departments - Art, Japanese art exhibit
    - Departments - Art, Probst exhibit, 1960 February
    - Departments - Art, Broderson and Wolfe, 1960 February
    - Departments - Art, Arts Council activities, 1959 February
    - Departments - Art, art exhibit, Union lobby, 1959 February
    - Departments - Art, art exhibit, Union lounge, 1958 October
    - Departments - Art, Broderson exhibit, 1957 June
    - Departments - Art, art winner, $50.00, 1957 May
    - Departments - Art, exhibit, 1956 November
    - Departments - Art, exhibit, East Campus library, 1956 November
    - Departments - Art, exhibit, East Campus library, 1956 November
    - Departments - Art, student contest winners, 1956 April
    - Departments - Art, Patrick and exhibit, 1962 April
    - Departments - Art, exhibit, East Campus, 1956 February
    - Departments - Art, exhibit, East Campus, 1956 January
    - Departments - Art, contest winners, 1955 May
    - Departments - Art, exhibit, East Campus, 1955 March
    - Departments - Art, Arts Council, award, 1954 June
    - Departments - Art, arts weekend, 1954 February 26
    - Departments - Art, Duke arts weekend, 1954 February 13
    - Departments - Art, exhibit, 1962 September
    - Departments - Art, exhibit, 1962 November
    - Departments - Art, exhibit, East Campus, 1963 March
    - Departments - Art, Arts Council, 1954 January 25
    - Departments - Art, exhibit, 1953 October 8
    - Departments - Art, exhibit, 1953 January 7
    - Departments - Art, art department, 1953 January
    - Departments - Art, Broderson's exhibit, East Campus, 1963 December
    - Departments - Art, Broderson exhibit, 1952 September 15
    - Departments - Art, Arts Council student, painting award, 1952 April 16
    - Departments - Art, art show, 1952 March 26
    - Departments - Art, art exhibit, 1951 December 3
    - Departments - Art, exhibit, 1951 November 19
    - Departments - Art, contest winner, 1951
    - Departments - Art, aesthetics, art and music, 1950 April 26
    - Departments - Art, house models, 1949 May 31
    - Departments - Art, fine arts, visitors and students viewing exhibits
    - Departments - Art, fine arts, exhibits in Woman's College Library, 1937 -1938
    - Departments - Art, fine arts, exhibits in Woman's College Library, 1930-1934
    - Departments - Art, art and music
    - Departments - Art, fine arts
    - Departments - Art, M. Maddry and art, 1960 May
    - Departments - Art, Leonard Kamsler, exhibit, 1964 February
    - Departments - Art, African art, 1978 October
    - Departments - Art, Forward Retreat by Mark Tansey
    - Departments - Art, copies, golf classic, 1983 April
    - Departments - Art, copy, 1985 January
    - Departments - Art, Institute of arts, 1986 December
  - Subject: Departments - Art (cont'd) (Box 18)
    - Departments - Art, artist copies, 1987 January
    - Departments - Art, copies, African mask, basket, Victorian painting, 1987 June
    - Departments - Art, copies, 1987 November
    - Departments - Art, objects, 1986 July
    - Departments - Art, museum lamp post, 1972 May
    - Departments - Art, museum, jade and porcelain, 1974
    - Departments - Art, museum, stairs at entrance, 1974 September
    - Departments - Art, new Brummer, 1970 January
    - Departments - Art, Chinese Exhibit, 1985 November
    - Departments - Art, coins
    - Departments - Art, arts festival, 1970 January
    - Departments - Art, Japanese paper tapestry, 1974 December
    - Departments - Art, old money, 1975 December
    - Departments - Art, sculptor, 1972
    - Departments - Art, Brummer collection, 1987 September
    - Departments - Art, Donatello exhibit, 1987 September
  - Subject: Departments - Biology
    - Departments - Biology, experimental, meeting, 1963 October
    - Departments - Biology, Livingston and African skull, 1961 September
    - Departments - Biology, Hussian story, Pakistan, 1960 May
    - Departments - Biology, biology college, 1958 April
    - Departments - Biology, radiation, 1961
    - Departments - Biology, cactus plants in biology hothouse, 1947 May 6
    - Departments - Biology, animals, 1937-1939
    - Departments - Biology, group, 1953 June 26
    - Departments - Biology, arctic research, 1980 July
    - Departments - Biology, labs, summer course
    - Departments - Biology, pufferfish, 1987 December
  - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, 1938
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, 1939
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, 1953
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, 1957
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, 1959
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, 1961
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, 1963
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, the Shamrock, boat
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, the Beveridge, boat
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, the Venus, boat
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, Bookhout
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, Paul Gross, Deryl Hart, Bookhout, 1960
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, Bookhout and class, 1962
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, Cortlow and Bookhout
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, Cortlow
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, Blomquist
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, IE Gray
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, composite used in bulletin
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, building dedication, 1954 July
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, building dedication, 1960 July
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, ship, trawler, 1961
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, dorms, 1963 May
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, vessel, 1963 March
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, Eastward, 1963
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, Eastward, laying keel, 1963 December 4
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, Eastward launching, 1964 May
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, Eastward dedication, 1964
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, Eastward launching, 1964 May
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, aerial, 1964 Fall
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, Eastward construction, 1964 October
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, Eastward construction, 1964 October
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, rock dredge on Eastward, 1969 February
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, dorm, 1966 June
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, John De Wolf, II, ship, 1977 October
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, upwelling project, 1977 August
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, Eastward, 1977 August
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, research ship, Hatteras, 1980 May
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, aquanautics model, 1984 February
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, 1982 August
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, feature, 1987 June
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, submarine, April
    - Departments - Biology - Marine Lab, 1973 November
  - Subject: Departments - Botany
    - Departments - Botany, 1938, 1943
    - Departments - Botany, 1949
    - Departments - Botany, group, 1954 July
    - Departments - Botany, plant interiors, 1956 January
    - Departments - Botany, hybrid corn, 1958 October
    - Departments - Botany, Danish visitor, 1959 September
    - Departments - Botany, visiting botanists, 1960 April
    - Departments - Botany, Don Stone, 1968 February
    - Departments - Botany, student
    - Departments - Botany, field trip
    - Departments - Botany, WSF, 1963 July
    - Departments - Botany, lab, 1987 April
  - Subject: Departments - Chemistry
    - Departments - Chemistry, 1937-1941
    - Departments - Chemistry, show, 1958 May
    - Departments - Chemistry, brochure, 1967 July
    - Departments - Chemistry, Dr. Bigelow's feature
    - Departments - Chemistry, frangible bullet, copies showing use of, 1947 January 29
    - Departments - Chemistry, labs, 1965 October
    - Departments - Chemistry, student winner, 1961
    - Departments - Chemistry, E. McHorter, 1961
    - Departments - Chemistry, experiment, 1957
    - Departments - Chemistry, show, 1957 Fall
    - Departments - Chemistry, conferences, 1957 November
    - Departments - Chemistry, shots for NSF, 1965 August
    - Departments - Chemistry, National SF shots, 1965 August
    - Departments - Chemistry, visitor, 1968 June
    - Departments - Chemistry, teaching awards, 1965 May
    - Departments - Chemistry, Carlton in lab, 1960 January
    - Departments - Chemistry, awards, 1965 May
    - Departments - Chemistry, winners, 1964 May
    - Departments - Chemistry, Fred Knape, student award, 1965 November
    - Departments - Chemistry, awards, 1967 May
    - Departments - Chemistry, check presentation, 1966 August
    - Departments - Chemistry, lab, 1967 November
    - Departments - Chemistry, Frosh teacher award, 1966 May
    - Departments - Chemistry, award winners, 1966 May
    - Departments - Chemistry, lab, 1960 February
    - Departments - Chemistry, Cherpak, lab, 1963 November
    - Departments - Chemistry, award, alumni register, 1958 April
    - Departments - Chemistry, award, 1959 May
    - Departments - Chemistry, award, 1959 May
    - Departments - Chemistry, award, 1961 June
    - Departments - Chemistry, Smith, lab, free radicals, 1963 November
    - Departments - Chemistry, labs
    - Departments - Chemistry, Turkish tobacco equipment, 1947 April 2
    - Departments - Chemistry, Dr. Gross, personal, 1942 July
    - Departments - Chemistry, Frank Avando, explosion, 1954 August
    - Departments - Chemistry, Hauser and student, 1957 April
    - Departments - Chemistry, research and students, 1951 October 3
    - Departments - Chemistry, conference, 1952 July 3
    - Departments - Chemistry, chemistry-zoology show, 1955 April
    - Departments - Chemistry, Klever and Saylor, 1954 March 8
    - Departments - Chemistry, show, 1954 March 12
    - Departments - Chemistry, Chem-Zoo show, officers, 1956 April
    - Departments - Chemistry, summer program, Dr. Bradsher, 1977 May
    - Departments - Chemistry, group, 1973 June
    - Departments - Chemistry, awards, 1972 May
    - Departments - Chemistry, dedication composite, 1968 December
    - Departments - Chemistry, executive conference, summer, 1976
    - Departments - Chemistry, executive group, summer, 1980 May
    - Departments - Chemistry, executives, 1986 May
    - Departments - Chemistry, executives, 1987 May
    - Departments - Chemistry, faculty, 1949
    - Departments - Chemistry, minorities, 1970
    - Departments - Chemistry, staff, 1970 October
    - Departments - Chemistry, symposium, retirement of Drs. Hobbs and Bradsher, 1979 April
    - Departments - Chemistry, conference group, 1975 June
  - Subject: Departments - Commonwealth Center
    - Departments - Commonwealth Center, students, register cover, 1957 January
    - Departments - Commonwealth Center, 1969 October
    - Departments - Commonwealth Center, books, 1969 September
    - Departments - Commonwealth Center, exterior, 1969 September
    - Departments - Commonwealth Center, Beinart, Spengler, 1969 April
  - Subject: Departments - Computation Center
    - Departments - Computation Center, 1969 November
  - Subject: Departments - Economics and Accounting
    - Departments - Economics and Accounting, Dr. Hoover, Russia trip, 1956 September
    - Departments - Economics and Accounting
    - Departments - Economics and Accounting, investment project, 1952 October 23
    - Departments - Economics and Accounting, award, 1952 May
    - Departments - Economics and Accounting, Dr. Black and scholar, 1962 September
    - Departments - Economics and Accounting, Beck, student accounting medal, 1956 March
    - Departments - Economics and Accounting, scholars, 1960 July
    - Departments - Economics and Accounting, scholarships, 1963 November
  - Subject: Departments - Education
    - Departments - Education, 1950 August 8
    - Departments - Education, faculty
    - Departments - Education, elementary, conference, 1962 June
    - Departments - Education, experiments in reading
    - Departments - Education, future teachers, conferences, 1952 October 18
    - Departments - Education, Future Teachers of America in NC, 1953 May 3
    - Departments - Education, Future Teachers of America, conferences, 1954 November
    - Departments - Education, Future Teachers of America, conferences, 1961 May
    - Departments - Education, high school guidance clinic, 1945 August
    - Departments - Education, guidance conference, 1954 March 5
    - Departments - Education, teachers conference, 1961 June
    - Departments - Education, teacher education conference, 1959 February
    - Departments - Education, GE representative, job interviews, 1956 March
    - Departments - Education, Bureau of Testing and Guidance, 1953 January 16
    - Departments - Education, testing and guidance bureau, 1952 February
    - Departments - Education, testing and guidance, 1952
    - Departments - Education, teaching, summer, Carr Jr. High, Ford Foundation, 1961 July
    - Departments - Education, teachers social, 1959 February
    - Departments - Education, teachers, social studies, 1956 February
    - Departments - Education, teachers education conference, 1958 February
    - Departments - Education, teachers dinner, 1953 June 25
    - Departments - Education, teachers conferences, 1954 October
    - Departments - Education, teachers conference, 1952 June 24
    - Departments - Education, teachers centennial speakers
    - Departments - Education, teachers from Caswell County, 1939
    - Departments - Education, teachers banquet, 1952 June 25
    - Departments - Education, school superintendent, principals, 1959 March
    - Departments - Education, teachers/supervisors conference, 1953 April
    - Departments - Education, teachers/student teaching conferences, 1956 February
    - Departments - Education, student teaching conference, 1955 February
    - Departments - Education, student teaching conference, 1954 February 26
    - Departments - Education, student teacher, 1953 February 6
    - Departments - Education, education seminar, 1950 March
    - Departments - Education, secondary school, counselors conference, 1964 October
    - Departments - Education, secondary school, counselors, 1963 October
    - Departments - Education, secondary school, counselors, 1961
    - Departments - Education, school counselors, 1961 October
    - Departments - Education, high school guidance counselors, 1961 October
    - Departments - Education, guidance counselors conference, 1962 September
    - Departments - Education, education conference, 1953 November 8
    - Departments - Education, conference, 1957 October
    - Departments - Education, education conference, 1960 February
    - Departments - Education, education conference, 1961 May
    - Departments - Education, story on potential school teacher, register, 1961
    - Departments - Education, National Assoc. of Teachers of singing, 1961 November
    - Departments - Education, AACTE conference, 1970 April
  - Subject: Departments - English
    - Departments - English, literary conference, writers, 1964 April
    - Departments - English, institute, 1950 July 5
    - Departments - English, panel, summer school, 1954 August
    - Departments - English, Hurlburt and assistant, 1960
    - Departments - English, conference, 1963 April
    - Departments - English, 1962 April
    - Departments - English, conference, 1961
    - Departments - English, conference, 1961 August
    - Departments - English, conference, 1961 May
    - Departments - English, conference, 1959 October
    - Departments - English, conference, summer, 1958
    - Departments - English, speaker, conference, 1957 June
    - Departments - English, conference, 1953 August
    - Departments - English, writers meeting, summer school, 1955
    - Departments - English, writers meeting, conference, 1953 July
    - Departments - English, writers forum, 1951 August 27
    - Departments - English, teachers conference, 1956 August
    - Departments - English, teachers meeting, 1952 July
    - Departments - English, staff, 1949 September 27
    - Departments - English, literary arts week, 1962 April
    - Departments - English, conference, 1947
    - Departments - English, Dr. Blackburn's writing group, 1946 May 12
    - Departments - English, Archives festival, visiting writers, 1963 April
    - Departments - English, Archives festival, 1966 April
  - Subject: Departments - Geology
    - Departments - Geology, meeting, 1969 April
    - Departments - Geology, 1956 May
    - Departments - Geology, boat, 1983 August
    - Departments - Geology, Bill Cromie, 1982 August
    - Departments - Geology, field study, seismic tests in Africa, 1985 February
    - Departments - Geology, research vessel, 1986 October
  - Subject: Departments - History (Box 19)
    - Departments - History, historians conference, 1956 October
    - Departments - History, Boyd portrait hanging, 1961
    - Departments - History, lecturer, 1968 August
    - Departments - History, conference, 1958 May
    - Departments - History, French history conference, 1958 February
    - Departments - History, history society officers, 1956 October
    - Departments - History, officers, 1958 May
    - Departments - History, Sunday worship
    - Departments - History, history essay award winners, 1956 May
    - Departments - History, historical sources meeting, 1954 April
    - Departments - History, students, alumni register, 1953 January 19
    - Departments - History, feature, 1970 July
  - Subject: Departments - Languages
    - Departments - Languages, German
    - Departments - Languages, German, library, 1951 October 15
    - Departments - Languages, language lab, 1967 February
    - Departments - Languages, slide rule for language lab, 1967 May
    - Departments - Languages, language lab, 1962 July
    - Departments - Languages, Latin American Studies meeting, 1954 February
    - Departments - Languages, Latin American scholars officers, 1954 February
    - Departments - Languages, Spanish Institute, 1948
    - Departments - Languages, conference, 1960 February
    - Departments - Languages, summer Spanish school, 1949 July 1
    - Departments - Languages, Spanish, summer school, 1951 June
    - Departments - Languages, Spanish school, 1950 June
    - Departments - Languages, Spanish school, summer, 1951
    - Departments - Languages, Spanish summer school, 1951 July 13
    - Departments - Languages, Spanish summer school, 1952 June 13
    - Departments - Languages, Spanish school, watermelon slicing, 1952 July
    - Departments - Languages, Spanish summer school, 1952 July
    - Departments - Languages, Spanish summer school, 1953 June 12
    - Departments - Languages, Spanish summer school, 1954 June
    - Departments - Languages, Spanish players, 1954 April 20
    - Departments - Languages, Spanish school, 1955 August
    - Departments - Languages, Spanish summer school, 1955 June
    - Departments - Languages, Spanish summer school, 1955 August
    - Departments - Languages, romance, summer workshop group, 1986 July
  - Subject: Departments - Mathematics
    - Departments - Mathematics, conference registration, summer school, 1955 June
    - Departments - Mathematics, Dr. Rankin with computer, 1947 April 24
    - Departments - Mathematics, conference, 1958 November
    - Departments - Mathematics, Dr. Rankin in charge, 1946 August
    - Departments - Mathematics, math institute, 1950 August
    - Departments - Mathematics, math institute, 1951 June
    - Departments - Mathematics, math institute, 1951 August
    - Departments - Mathematics, math institute dinner honoring Rankin, 1952 August
    - Departments - Mathematics, math institute, 1952 August 16
    - Departments - Mathematics, retired military taking math, 1958 August
    - Departments - Mathematics, retired officers, math class, 1962 August
    - Departments - Mathematics, retired officers, 1962 April
    - Departments - Mathematics, retired officers, math program, 1964 July
    - Departments - Mathematics, retired officers, math class, 1961 June
    - Departments - Mathematics, computer, new, 1961 May
  - Subject: Departments - Philosophy
    - Departments - Philosophy
  - Subject: Departments - Physical Education
    - Departments - Physical Education, visiting speaker, 1966 April
    - Departments - Physical Education, Hanya Holm, 1939 April 3
    - Departments - Physical Education, John Lanno(?), baseball
    - Departments - Physical Education, pool
    - Departments - Physical Education, women's, 1950
    - Departments - Physical Education, tests, 1966 May
    - Departments - Physical Education, story, alumni register, 1961
    - Departments - Physical Education, big four winners, 1980 April
    - Departments - Physical Education, Roy Skinner, 1975 September
  - Subject: Departments - Physics
    - Departments - Physics, visit to computer lab, bubble chamber
    - Departments - Physics, equipment, 1952 January